insurance company like sunlight pro-life
and so on in support so I am financial
advisor of Sun Life Insurance company
and Guston is
financial advisor
first thing they got going nothing is to
look for a financial advisor the running
for manager or what we call the field
manager or manager candidate
Financial advisory
financial advisor Andrea
[Music]
financial advisor the third step is
a stimulated exams category which are
the vul or young with investment
traditional
Health protection
simulated
insurance commission after simulated
certificate or electronic certificate
one of the requirements in
or what we call the Sun Life training
course so 10 days allotted online
duties videos
claim
blah
of course you simulated
sltc the next step is
requirements
insurance commission 929 exam is
a financial advisor these are the
requirements
and four pieces and a one by one ID
pictures take note yellow background
usually white background
this time and yellow background the
second one is an exam permit
advisor
and the other one for ACM
financial advisors
[Music]
the next one is the latest filed income
tax return
another one is photocopy of tax
identification number or young atington
[Music]
number
that was and if not employed letter of
source of income
employed source of income
financial advisor another requirement is
an valid National Bureau of
Investigation or nbip grants
[Music]
number eight photocopy of me runs from
previous employer if not currently
employed or photocopy of Company ID if
currently employed number nine valid ID
of signatory from the clearance
number 10 photocopy of licensing exam
result
Young Insurance Commission number 11
original official receipt for payment of
Licensing fee so 3030 pesos
number 12 certificate of Authority or
UNCA application form notarized
traditional and vul so
application form or certificate of
authority
400 pesos
number 13 undergo medical exam if 40
years old and above to be done after
coding
is 40 years old
number 14 if currently a government
employee letter from management of the
government office allowing recruit to
sell life insurance while employed
government
number 15 sltc certificate
certificates
and life training course
one of the requirements number 16 I see
online stimulated certificate
online simulated exam
certificate and screenshot
stamp
[Music]
foreign
brighter life with Sun Life
[Music]
Sun Life Insurance company so um
financial advisors and for sure
life insurance Health protection
investment and free to message me and
and winning Pokemon
life insurance Health protection and
investment
financial advisor of Sun Life stay safe
and get blessed